cleopatraschoice.com 2017-06-18

# Privacy Policy

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

We take your privacy very seriously! We HATE Spam just as much as you do.

Natural Lifestyle Brands, Inc. (“Cleopatra's Choice”) respects your privacy. We have created this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to inform you about how we collect and use information about you on and through CleopatrasChoice.com (the “Web Site”). 

### Information We Collect, Store and Use

We collect and store information that you enter into the Web Site or that you provide to our Customer Service Representatives. For example, when you open an account or place an order, we collect and store some or all of the following information that you provide: name, billing address, shipping address, email address, telephone number, credit card number and expiration date ("Personal Information"). This information is used to provide the products and services that you have ordered or requested, to process and ship orders, to send order and shipping confirmations and to provide customer service. Some of this information may also be used to contact you about new products, sales, promotions, special offers, and events, product and customer surveys and new site features, unless you have opted not to receive promotional communications in connection with this Web Site.

We collect and store certain other information automatically whenever you interact with our Web Site. For example, we collect your IP address, browser information and reference site domain name every time you visit the Web Site. We also collect information regarding customer traffic patterns and site usage. This information is used to analyze and improve the Web Site and to provide you with a fulfilling shopping experience.

Also, like many Web Sites, we use "cookies", which are files stored on your computer's hard drive by your browser. Cookies help us to identify account holders and to optimize their shopping experience. Cookies also allow us to hold selections in a shopping cart when a user leaves our Site without checking out. Most browsers accept cookies automatically but allow you to disable them. We recommend that you leave cookies "turned on" so that we can offer you a better shopping experience on our Web Site.

We also may combine information we collect from you through your use of the Web Site with information we collect and store about you that we receive off line or from other sources. We use this information to enable us to update and correct the information contained in our database, better understand you as a customer and to provide product recommendations and special offers that we think will interest you.

### Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. We do not sell or ship any items ordered through our Web Site directly to anyone who we know to be under the age of 13.

### Use and Disclosure of Information

We do not disclose your Personal Information except with your consent or as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your Personal Information with our affiliates, strategic and/or marketing partners and with our service providers. Certain of our affiliates and service providers may also disclose your Personal Information to their affiliates and service providers whom they engage to perform services related to the Web Site or the operation of our business. Examples of these services include payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, order fulfillment and shipping, marketing and promotional material distribution, Web Site evaluation, data analysis and, where applicable, data cleansing. Our service providers are authorized to use your Personal Information only in connection with the services they are engaged to perform.

We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that: the law or legal process requires it; we have received a valid administrative request from a law enforcement agency; or such release is necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Cleopatra's Choice, or any of our affiliates, service providers, customers or others.

We may disclose non-personal information with our marketing partners, advertisers and others from time to time. Examples of such non-personal information include the number of users who visited the Web Site during a specific time period or purchased a specific product through the Web Site. This information generally is shared in an aggregated form.

### Security

We have implemented reasonable security measures, including Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology, to protect the Personal Information that we collect from you. Your payment information and personal information is encrypted when transmitted to us and are stored in a secure environment. If you place an order through the Web Site, you may be asked, but are not required, to set up an account and provide an email address and password. You must provide an appropriate email address and password in order to access account information. In order to help protect your personal information further, you should use a unique password and not provide your password to others. If you wish to cancel your password, or if you become aware of any loss, theft or unauthorized use of your password, please contact us by email at support@cleopatraschoice.com or by phone at 800-925-4232.

Sometimes you may get a message that some pages on the Web Site are not secure. This is a security alert message which results from browsing to a non-secure page from a secure page. We only secure the pages on the Web Site that contain your personal information. This helps us keep the site quick and efficient. If you are ever concerned about the security of a page, simply look at the URL. If it begins with a "https://" instead of "http://" the site is secure.

Unfortunately, however, no transmission of data over the Internet and no data storage is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under our control to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your Personal Information, we (including our service providers) cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk.

### Accessing, Correcting and Updating Personal Information?

You can access, correct and update certain Personal Information that you have provided to us by clicking on "My Account" at the top or on the bottom under “Quick Links” on each Web Site page

### Opting Out of Receiving Promotional Communications

There are several ways in which you can tell us whether or not you want to receive promotional communications from us. When you set up an account, log into "My Account" or place an order, you will have an opportunity to make or change to your preferences in this regard. You also will have an opportunity to change your subscription preferences, including unsubscribing, by clicking on the "update profile" hyperlink contained in promotional emails we send you.

### Linking to Other Sites?

Our Web Site may contain links to other sites operated by our parent, affiliates companies or third parties. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to information gathered through these other sites and that we are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices or contents of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave our Web Site and to read the privacy policies of each and every site that you visit.

### Contests and Sweepstakes

When we run a contest or sweepstakes relating to our Web Site, it will be accompanied by a set of rules. The rules for each contest/sweepstakes will specify how the information you submit for your entry will be used and disclosed, and may be different than as described in this Privacy Policy.

### International Users

The Web Site is hosted from the United States. Users located outside of the United States consent to the transfer of their data to the United States for processing and use in accordance with this Policy.

### Your California Privacy Rights

Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, if you live in the State of California, you may request certain information about the type of your Personal Information that we share with third parties for direct marketing purposes and the identity of any such third party. Once per calendar year, California residents may request this information by contacting us by e-mail at support@cleopatraschoice.com, by phone at 800-925-4232 or by writing to us at: Cleopatra's Choice 543 Country Club Drive, Suite B123 Simi Valley, CA 93065, USA .  

### Additional Information.

If you choose to visit our Web Site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use including, but not limited to, limitations of damages and application of the law of the State of California. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO NEGLIGENCE, SHALL CLEOPATRA'S CHOICE, OR OUR PARENT, OR ANY OF OUR AFFILIATED COMPANIES OR SERVICE PROVIDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM THE USE OF THE INFORMATION OR MATERIALS ON THE CLEOPATRASCHOICE.COM WEB SITE, EVEN IF CLEOPAT'RA'S CHOICE OR OUR PARENT, OR ANY OF OUR AFFILIATED COMPANIES OR SERVICE PROVIDERS, OR AN AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE OF CLEOPATRA'S CHOICE OR OUR PARENT, OR ANY OF OUR AFFILIATED COMPANIES OR SERVICE PROVIDERS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

### Acceptance of Terms

By using our Web Site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. By providing Personal Information to us through the Web Site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy with respect to the collection and use of your Personal Information. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, do not use the Web Site. Your continued use of the Web Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean that you accept those changes accordingly.

### How Will I Be Informed About Changes Regarding This Privacy Policy?

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we modify this Privacy Policy, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on the Web Site. We may also post a notice on the Web Site or send an email describing the changes. You should check the Web Site regularly to see if any recent changes to this Privacy Policy have occurred.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact the Site Customer Service Department by e-mail at support@cleopatraschoice.com, by phone at 800-925-4232 or by writing to us at: Cleopatra's Choice 543 Country Club Drive, Suite B123 Simi Valley, CA 93065, USA

Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [click here](https://reports.web.analytics.yahoo.com/optout,OptOut.vm?domain=a.analytics.yahoo.com).
